Guide to the Wesley C. Salmon Papers, 1950-2003 ASP.2003.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Correspondence, 1960-2010; 1963-2001; I.
  - Correspondents - E, 5.
    - Earman, John, 1967-1998 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Eastman, William, 1966-1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Eaton, Marcia, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Eccles, John, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Ecker, Michael, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Eckhardt, William, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Ed, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Edmonds, Margaret, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Edwards, Paul, 1982-1987 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Edwards, Richard, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Eells, Ellery, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Ehrlich, Philip, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Eilstein, Helena, 1993-1998 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Eisenberg, Paul, 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Ellenberger, Leroy, 1986-1996 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Ellet, Fredrick, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Ellis, Brian, 1966-1971 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Elugardo, Reinaldo, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Embree, Lester, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Emmerson, Susan, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Enc, Berent, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Endeavour, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Ennis, Robert, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Ericson, David, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Erkenntnis, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Erwin, Keith, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Essler, William, 1983-1994 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Evan, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Correspondents - F, 6.
    - Faggetter, Rachel, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Fagot, Anne, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Fair, David, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Falk, Arthur, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Fang, J., 1969 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Fararo, Thomas, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Farber, Paul, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Farley, Miriam, 1965-1971 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Farre, George, 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Farrell, Daniel, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Fawkes, David, 1976-1989 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Feibleman, James, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Feigl, Herbert, 1963-1975 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Feinberg, Joel, 1965-1987 (Box 5, Folder 42-43)
    - Feldman, Gordon, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Feldman, Seymour, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Fenstad, Jens Erik, 1983-1998 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Ferre, Frederick, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Ferrell, Russ, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Festa, Roberto, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Feyerabend, Paul, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Fetzer, James, 1968-1997 (Box 5, Folder 51-53)
    - Findlay, Isobel, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Fine, Arthur, 1972-1977 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Finkelstein, Michael, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Finn, Bernard, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Fisher, John, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Fisher, Philip, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Fisher, R.B., 1975 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Fisk, Milton, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Fleetwood, Hugh, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Fleming, Gordon, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Flichman, Eduardo, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Fogelin, Robert, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Foley, Richard, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Ford, Andrew, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Forester, Malcolm, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Forester, Michael, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Forge, John, 1979-1989 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Forrai, Gabor, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Forrester, John, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Foster, J.F., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Fox, John, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Frasca-Spada, Marina, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Franceschi, Ginafranco, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Francis, Russell, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Frank, Paul, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Frankena, William, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Frankfurt, Harry, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Frantz, Charles, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Franz, Frank, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Franzel, Tom, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Fred and Ann, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Friedman, Joel, 1974-1978 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Free Press, The, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Freeman, Eugene, 1968-1971 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Freeman, Lisa, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Freudenthal, H., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Friedman, Michael, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Friedson, Michael, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Frigg, Robert, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Frity, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Fry, Martha, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Fuentes, Cesar, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Fuller, Maynard, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Fultz, Nancy, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Furth, Monty, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Correspondents - G, 7.
    - Gadol, Eugene, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Galavotti, Maria Carla, 1972-1998 (Box 6, Folder 31-32)
    - Gale, George, 1976-1998 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Gale, Richard, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Garcia, Gisela, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Gardenfors, Peter, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Gardener, Martin, 1967 -1985 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Gardner, Michael, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Garfinkle, Alan, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Garretty, Helen, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Garsen, Robert, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Garver, Newton, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Gaude, Albert, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Gauker, Chris, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Gauthier, David, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Gayle, Richard, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Gemes, Ken, 1988-1998 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - George, 1964-1996 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Gettier, Edmund, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Ghins, Michel, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Giannoni, Carlo, 1971-1979 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Giansiracusa, Joseph, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Gibbs, Peter, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Giere, Ronald, 1966-1991 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Gifford, Fred, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Gillen, H.W., 1971 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Gillies, Donald, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Gillispie, Charles, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Gimbel, Steve, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Gindhart, Mary, 1966-1971 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Ginet, Carl, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Girill, T.R., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Gisolo, Gisella, 1996-2000 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Gladstein, Gerald, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Glennan, Stuart, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Glotzbach, Philip, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Glymour, Clark, 1966-1993 (Box 6, Folder 67-68)
    - Godambe, V.P., 1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Goe, George, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Goheen, John, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Goldberg, Bruce, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Goldfield, Tammy, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Golding, Martin, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Goldstein, Jack, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Goldstein, Leon, 1985-1989 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Gonzalez, Wenceslao, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Good, Jack, 1980-1997 (Box 7, Folder 10, Unknown item \)
    - Goodman, Michael, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Goosens, Williams, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Gordon, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Gordon, Robert, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Gordon, Scott, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Gorovitz, Sam, 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Gorski, Ann, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Grace, Jennifer, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Graham, Loren, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Grandy, Richard, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Grandy, Walter, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Grant, Edward, 1966-1997 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Gray, Alex, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Grecu, Constantin, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Green, Mitch, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Green, Paul Phillip, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Green, Robert, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Greene, Mary, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Greeno, James, 1965-1978 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Gregg, Nancy, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Grene, Majorie, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Grim, Patrick, 1990-1995 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Grimes, Tom, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Gropen, Beverley, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Gros Louis, Kenneth, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Gross, Damon, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Grossman, Neal, 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Grover, Dorothy, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Grunstra, Bernard, 1965-1973 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Grunbaum, Adolf, 1963-1999 (Box 7, Folder 40-50)
    - Gucker, Frank, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Gunderson, Gary, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Gunderson, Keith, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Gupta, Yogesh, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Gustavsson, Roger, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondents - H-I, 8.
    - Hackett, Edward, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Hackett, William, 1967-1979 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Hacking, Ian, 1965-1997 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Hadden, Richard, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Hadgopoulos, Demetrius, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Hajek, Petr, 1974-2000 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Halcomb, Jay, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Halberstadt, William, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Hall, Diana Long, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Haller, Rudolf, 1976-1991 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Hameed, Abdul, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Hamilton, David, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Hampshire, Stuart, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Handy, Rollo, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Hanen, Marsha, 1969-1975 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Hank, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Hanna, Joseph, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Hannaway, Owen, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Hansen, Alexander, undated (Box 8, Folder 24, Unknown item \)
    - Hansen, Kaj, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Hanson, Norwood, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Hanson, William, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Hanzel, Igor, 1990-1998 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Harari- Eslel, Orna, undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Hardcastle, Gary, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Hardegree, Gary, 1974-1983 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Harder, Allen, 1971-1977 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Hardwick, Charles, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Hare, Richard, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Haring, Ellen, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Harmsen, Olga, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Harper, Charles, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Harper, John, undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Harpers & Row Publishers, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Harre, Ron, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Harris, Kay, undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Harrison, L., 1988 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Harrison, Stephen, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Harsanyi, John, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Harvard University Press, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Harward, Donald, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Hattink, J.F., 1988 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Hauser, David, 1977-1981 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Hausman, Dan, 1984-1987 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Hayes, Larry, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Heany, Patrick, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Heelan, Patrick, 1971-1989 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Heidelberger, Michael, 1996-1999 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Heinz, John, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Heise, Gerhard, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Held, Matthew, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Hellman, Geoffrey, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Hellmuth, William, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Helm, Mr., 1972 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Hempel, Carl, 1965-1992 (Box 8, Folder 60-61)
    - Heniser, Virgil, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Henninger, Ernest, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Henrik von Wright, George, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Henry, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Herbison, Gerald, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Hessler, Edward, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Hetzel, Frederick, 1966-1984 (Box 8, Folder 68, Unknown item 66)
    - Heverly, Gerald, 1990-1994 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Hiatt, Howard, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - High, Dallas, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Hight, Marc, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Hill, Brian, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Hilpenen, Risto, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Hintikka, Jaakko, 1965-1998 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Hitch, Harriet, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Hitchcock, Christopher, 1991-1998 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Hitchen, O.M., 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Hitt, James, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Hiz, Henry, 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Hlavaty, Vaclav, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - Hobbs, Milton, undated (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - Hochstatter, Timothy, 1966-1969 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - Hodges, Niltrid, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Hoekema, David, 1985-1988 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Hoerster, Norbert, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Hoffman, Eric, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Hogarch, Mark, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Holdcraft, David, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Hollinger, Amos, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Holton, Gerald, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Home, R.W., 1971-1997 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Hon, Giora, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Hoogwegt, M., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Hooker, C.A., 1972-1986 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Hope, Greg, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Hord, Richard, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Hormel, James, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Horirch, Paul, 1980-1989 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Howard, Don, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Howard, John, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Howell, Thomas, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Hoy, Ron, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Hubin, Don, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Hubner, Adolf, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Huff, Thomas, 1972-1984 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Hugayet, Rehat, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Huggett, Nick, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Hughes, R.I.G., 1991 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Hull, David, 1967-1999 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Hull, Elaine, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Hull, Richard, 1967-2000 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Humphreys, Paul, 1977-1994 (Box 9, Folder 30-32)
    - Humphreys, Paul, 1974-1987 (Box 9, Folder 38-41)
    - Humphrey, Ted, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Hunt, G.M.K., 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Hunter, David, 1970-1980 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Ihara, Craig, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Iru, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Correspondents - J-K, 9.
    - Jackson, Howard, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Jackson, Matthew, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Jackson, Sherman, 1967-1978 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Jan, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Janis, Allen, 1976-1980 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Jarrett, Jon, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Jauch, J.M., undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Jean, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Jeffrey, Ricahard, 1971-1989 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Jelin, Victor, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Jen, 1968-1991 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Jerry, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Jewell,Robert, 1964-1967 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Jim, 1965-1974 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Jobe, Evan, 1970-1990 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - John, 1972-1982 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Johnson, Conrad, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Johnson, Edward, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Johnson, Glenn, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Johnson, Norman, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Johnson, Oliver, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Johnson, Walter, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Joksch, Hans, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Jones, Lee, 1981-1990 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Jongsma, Calvin, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Joravsky, David, 1965-1989 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Jorge, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Journal of Philosophy, 1967-1995 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Josephson, John, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Judy, 1973-1978 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Juhl, Cory, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Kacena, Carolyn, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Kaemmer, Beverly, 1989-1991 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Kadish, M.R., 1965-1979 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Kahane, Howard, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Kaiser, Mattias, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Kalish, Donald, 1965-1975 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Kamlah, Andreas, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Kaplan, David, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Kardon, Peter, 1991-1994 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Karlsson, Mikael, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Kassander, Richard, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Katz, Jonathan, 1983-1988 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Kaufer, Stephan, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Kauffman, Robert, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Kaufman, Arnold, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Kaufman, Burton, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Kawalec, Pawel, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Kay, Charles, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Kay, Ernest, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Keane, Brian, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Kearns, Jean, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Kearns, John, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Kekes, John, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Kelly, Kevin, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Kelly, Patrick, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Ken, 1966-1985 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Kenner, Lionel, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Kennick, W.E., 1969 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Kent, Daryl, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Keren, Gideon, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Kessel, Harlan, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Kiam-Laine, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Killeen, Peter, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Kim, Jaegwon, 1967-1993 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - King, Gerald, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - King, John, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Kirk, John, 1963-1971 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Kish, Leslie, 1977-1987 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Kitcher, Philip, 1986-1998 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Klawon, Robin, 1984-1991 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Klein, Bruce, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Klein, Peter, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Klemke, Elmer, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Klenk, Virgina, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Kline, David, 1977-1988 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Kluwer Academic Publishers, 1992-1998 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Knoch, John, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Koda, Sammuel, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Koecher, K.F., 1967 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Koehler, Peter, 1988-1997 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Koertge, Noretta, 1973-1998 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Kohler, Eckehart, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Kollander, Mary, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Kooijam, J.M.W., 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Kolodziej, Edward, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Komendzinski, Tomasz, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Koning, Gert, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Kopec, Judy, undated (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Koppel, Moshe, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Korb, Kevin, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Kordig, Carl, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Korner, Stephan, 1963-1978 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Kovalchick, Karen, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Kourany, Janet, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Kraemer, Eric, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Kramarisyk, Wolfgang, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Krips, Henry, 1970-1983 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Kreithen, Amy, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Kronz, Fredrick, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Kruger, Lorenz, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Kuhn, Thomas, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Kulpers, Annie, 1980-1992 (Box 10, Folder 62-63)
    - Kvart, Igal, 1975-1989 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Kyburg, Henry, 1963-1981 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Correspondents - L, 10.
    - La Monte, Edward, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Lacey, Hugh, 1966-1970 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Lacey, Matthew, 1970-1974 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Ladd, John, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Ladd, Roz, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Ladkin, Peter, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Ladyman, James, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Lakatos, Imre, 1965-1973 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Lamb, Ursula, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Lambert, Karel, 1965-1986 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Lancaster, Katharine, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Lance, Mark, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Landucci, Sergio, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Langan, Thomas, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Lange, Marc, 1989-1994 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Langer, Larry, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Lango, John, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Langton, Chris, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Larkin, P.A., 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Larson, Madeline, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Laudan, Larry, 1970-1986 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Lauter, H.A., 1964 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Lawson, Warren, 1967-1969 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Laymon, Ron, 1975-1980 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Lazara, Vince, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Lazerowitz, Alice, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Lean, Martin, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Le Blanc, Hugues, 1965-1975 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Lehman, Hugh, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Lehrer, Keith, 1968-1973 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Leinfellner, Werner, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Lemer, Ken, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Lemond, Ed, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Lenoir, Tim, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Leonard, Henry, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Leplin, Jarrett, 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Lerer, Shimon, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Leslie, Michael, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Lesure, Alan, 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Levi, Isaac, 1965-1986 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Levine, Milton, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Levine, Vicki, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Levison, Arnold, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Levy, Edwin, 1964-1982 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Lewis, Albert, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Lewis, David, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Lewis, Douglas, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Lewis, Michael, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Li, Xian-Kun, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Lichtenerg, Don, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Lieberson, Stanley, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Linda, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Lindell, Edward, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Lindgren, Ralph, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Lindsay, Bruce, 1964-1968 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Lins, Mario, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Linsky, Leonard, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Lipton, Peter, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Lisa, undated (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Little, Robert, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Livingston College, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Long, Eugene, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Longacre, William, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Looney, Dennis, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Loptson, Peter, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Los, Jerzy, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Louch, A.R., 1976 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Lu, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Lucas, Sylvia, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Lucci, Michael, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Lukenbach, Sidney, 1976-1983 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Ludwig, Cameron, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Lugg, Andrew, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Luper-Foy, Steven, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Lycan, William, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Lyon, Ardon, 1973-1981 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Lyre, Holger, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Correspondents - M, 11.
    - MacBain, William, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - MacDonald, Jim, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - MacFarlane, John, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - Machamer, Peter, 1979-1994 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - Mackenzie, Patrick, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Mackie, Jon, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - Macmilliam Press Ltd, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Madden, Edward, 1965-1968 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - Maddy, Penelope, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Maher, James, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - Maher, Patrick, 1982-1991 (Box 11, Folder 74-75)
    - Makinde, Moses, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - Man, Si-Wai, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Manaktala, Gita, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Mantell, Suzanne, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Manwaring, William, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Marc, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Marcus, Ruth, 1971-1981 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Mardiros, Anthony, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Mares, Ed, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Margolis, Joseph, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Mark, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Marks, J.L., 1975 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Markusic, Michael, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 12)